(Raj:)I really don't get your problem
with birds.
(Sheldon:)The question you should be asking is,
what is their problem with me?
(Sheldon:)My first memory, a hummingbird
dive-bombing my stroller...
(Sheldon:)...to get at the apple juice
in my sippy cup.
(Raj:)Hummingbirds are pretty.
(Sheldon:)Hummingbirds are the vampires
of the flower world.
(Raj:)Still my first choice
for an ankle tattoo.
(Raj:)Or a dolphin. I go back and forth.
Age 7, a blood-thirsty chicken
chases me up a tree.
Age 12, a magpie tries to steal
the retainer out of my mouth.
Age 16, a parrot in a pet store
calls me fat ass.
(Sheldon:)Need I go on?
(Raj:)Yes, please.
This is way better than the movie, heh.
(Howard:)All right, Sheldon.
Your bird death ray is ready.
(Sheldon:)It's not a death ray. It's just a little
uItrasonic blast to scare him off.
(Sheldon:)Trust me, if I had a death ray,
I wouldn't be Iiving here.